Inventory of the Great Britain Ministry of Information propaganda
Hoover Institution Archives
- Pamphlets and leaflets, 1938-1949
  - "Glass Protection in Shops," Ministry of Home Security (Box 3)
  - "God Defend the Right," Fosh and Cross Ltd., London (Box 12)
  - "Gold Coast for Victory," Cockayne & Co. Ltd. (Box 1)
  - "Government and Industry," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 7)
  - "Great Britain - The World's Best Customer,", 1945 (Box 16)
  - "Great Britain and Germany: The Issues of War," Halifax, Lord, England, 1940 (Box 2)
  - "Great Britain: To-Day and To-morrow," British Ministry of Information, Great Britain, 1944 (Box 2)
  - "The Greatest Crusade," Sanders, Phillips & Co (Box 14)
  - Greek language pamphlet (Box 1)
  - "Groot-Brittainië's beide vloten" (Box 12)
  - "Groot-Brittainië's industrieele prestatie," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "Groot-Brittainië's Royal Air Force (Box 11)
  - "Grow for Winter as well as Summer," Ministry of Agriculture and Fisheries (Box 12)
  - "The Growth of the Empire Commonwealth," Harrison & Sons Ltd., London (Box 14)
  - "The Growth of the Empire Commonwealth," J.A. Williamson, L.T.A. Robinson Ltd., London (Box 13)
  - "A guerra submarina" (Box 10)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 5-7 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 11-15 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 16-20 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 21-25 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 27-30 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 31-35 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 36-40 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre illustrée" No. 41, 43, 47, 48, 56 (Box 15)
  - "La guerre sous-marine" (Box 10)
  - "Halifaxes Over the Ruhr" (Box 8)
  - "Handbook on Persia," Ministry of Information, Serial Map Service, London (Box 2)
  - "The Harm Japan Has Done Us, Part I: Economic; and Part II: Psychological," Ministry of Information, 1944 (Box 7)
  - "Harvest Home: The British Farmer at War," H.M. Stationery Office (Box 1)
  - "Harvest Home: The Offical Story of the Great Flood of 1947 and Their Sequel," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 1)
  - "High Quality Silage," Ministry of Information & Ministry of Agriculture (Box 5)
  - "His Majesty's Ships," Official Permission, London, 1942 (Box 1)
  - "'Hitler Won't Win!'," Clarke & Sherwell Ltd., England, 1941 (Box 8)
  - "Hitler's War on the Catholic Church," Spottiswoode, Ballantyne & Co. Ltd., England (Box 8)
  - "Hitler's Words and Hitler's Deeds," England (Box 2)
  - "Home Guard, Southern Railway in Pictures," McCorquodale & Co. Ltd., London (Box 14)
  - "Honneur et patrie," Stevens & B, 1944 (Box 10)
  - "Honneur Patrie," The Franco-British Publishing Co., 1941 (Box 10)
  - "The House of Wadham Went to War," E.T. Symons (Box 10)
  - "Housing: The Magnitude of the Problem," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "How Hitler Made the War," Ministry of Information, London (Box 17)
  - "How to Keep Well in Wartime," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1943 (Box 2)
  - "How to Protect Your Home, Your Business, Your City," Ministry of Home Security (Box 4)
  - "How to Put up Your Morrison Shelter," Ministry of Home Security (Box 3)
  - "I believe...," Ministry of Information & H.M. Stationery Office (Box 4)
  - "I have changed my mind," England (Box 4)
  - "Ici Radio-Belgique," British Broadcasting Corporation (Box 10)
  - "The Illustrated London News," Office, Commonwealth House, London, 1941 (Box 14)
  - "Immortal Fame...," S.P. & Co. Ltd. (Box 2)
  - "Important Request," Cockayne & Co., Ltd., London (Box 7)
  - "In Action in Taranto...," S.P. & Co. Ltd. (Box 2)
  - "L'Inde en guerre," Sir George Dunbar, 1940 (Box 16)
  - "India and Burma Squadrons of the R.A.F.," L.T.A. Robinson, Ltd., London (Box 3)
  - "India at War," Sir George Dunbar, His Majesty's Stationery Office, England (Box 8)
  - "India at War," England (Box 2)
  - "India at War," George Pulman & Sons, Ltd. (Box 10)
  - "India at War: Rising Flood of Vast Resources," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1941 (Box 3)
  - "The Indian War Effort," Times Publishing Company, England, 1939 (Box 5)
  - "L'industrie anglaise sur le front de l'arrière," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "Information for Speakers: The Malay Peninsula," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Information for Speakers: The People of Malaya," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Information for Speakers: The Story of the Malay Peninsula Part I-II," Ministry of Information (Box 7)
  - "Information for Speakers: The War Against Japan," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Inspection and Repair of Respirators and Oilskin Clothing," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1940 (Box 6)
  - "International Co-Operation against the Locust," Ministry of Information, 1944 (Box 7)
  - "International Students: 1942-1943 Record of Struggle," International Council of Students, Great Britain (Box 2)
  - "Introducing the Eastern Dependences," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1949 (Box 2)
  - "Introducing West Africa," British Infromation Services, New York (Box 7)
  - "Iran," K.H.K. (Box 4)
  - "Italian Atrocities in Libya," Amir Shakib Arslan (Box 9)
  - "Italy Stabs Herself in the Back" (in 2 languages) (Box 14)
  - "It's a Long Way to London" (Box 4)
  - "Jamaica for Victory," Cockayne & Co. Ltd. (Box 1)
  - "Japan Menaces World Trade" (Box 3)
  - "Japan: The Place and Population," Ministry of Information (Box 13)
  - "Japanese Aggression!" (Box 7)
  - "The Japanese Army: Its Rise to Power and Its Influence," Ministry of Information (Box 7)
  - "Japanese Co-Prosperity" (Box 7)
  - "Japanese Tyrants in Korea" (Box 5)
  - "Japan's Mercantile Shipping Routes" (Box 3)
  - "Japan's War Strength: The Present Position," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Jeune de 25 ans," Stevens & B. (Box 2)
  - "John Britain - Post War," British Information Services, New York City, 1946 (Box 9)
  - "Journal de bord de la R.A.F., " (Box 8)
  - "Journal du Camp" No. 1-20, July-August, 1940 (Box 17)
  - "Justice, Liberty, Truth" Comic (Box 4)
  - "Justification," Fosh and Cross Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Keeping Them Flying" (Box 8)
  - "Kenya for Victory," Cockayne & Co., Ltd. (Box 8)
  - "Kill that Lie!" Ministry of Information, England (Box 10)
  - "Kill That Rat! It's Doing Hitler's work!" Sanders, Phillips & Co., Ltd., England (Box 3)
  - "Know Your Army No.1, 2, 3 Food Related (Box 13)
  - "Krigen Til Sjos," G.P.D., 1943 (Box 14)
  - "Krigen Til Sjos," Norwegian Publishers Ltd., 1943 (Box 14)
  - "Lake Victoria: The K.U.R. Steamer Arrives," British Information Services, New York City (Box 5)
  - "Land Warfare," H.M. Stationery Office Press, 1939 (Box 3)
  - "Landbruget kaemper ogsaa" (Box 14)
  - "L'aviation anglaise" (Box 12)
  - "Leprosy," B & M Ltd. (Box 6)
  - "A Letter to Susan," B & M Ltd. (Box 3)
  - "Letters to the British Population," 1940 (Box 17)
  - "The Liberation of Europe" (Box 11)
  - "Librarianship," His Majesty's Stationery Office, 1949 (Box 7)
  - "Life in Nigeria," B & M Ltd. (Box 2)
  - "The Life of a West African Cocoa Farmer," B & M Ltd. (Box 6)
  - "The Listening Post" (Box 10)
  - "Little Ships of the Royal Navy" (Box 10)
  - "Local Studies," Bishop Aukland, His Majesty's Sationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 5)
  - "The Locust," B & M Ltd. (Box 7)
  - "London Airport," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 7)
  - "London: Headquarters of Free Europe," L.T.A. Robinson, Limited, London (Box 2)
  - "Look, Read, and Judge" (Box 3)
  - "Pa lopende band de Britske fabrikkene i krig," His Majesty's Stationary Office, London, 1944 (Box 14)
  - "Lord Halifax Reviews the Situation," Halifax, Lord, H.M. Stationery Office Press (Box 1)
  - "Lord Lloyd Salutes the Colonial Empire at War" (Box 2)
  - "De macht van de koopvaardijvloot" (Box 11)
  - "A Magna Carta for the Free Nations" (Box 12)
  - "Make Your Home Safe Now," Ministry of Information (Box 3)
  - "Make Your Home Safe Now," Ministry of Information & Ministry of Home Security (Box 5)
  - "Malta a la ofensiva" (Box 9)
  - "Malta" (Box 9)
  - "Malte passe à l'attaque" (Box 9)
  - "Man or Beast?" Kellher, Hudson & Kearns, Ltd., England (Box 2)
  - "Man Power," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1944 (Box 5)
  - "Map of China," Fosh and Cross, England, 1944 (Box 11)
  - "Map of Military Operations in North and East Africa," F & C Ltd. (Box 7)
  - "Map of Military Operations in North and East Africa," Fosh & Cross Ltd. (Box 11)
  - "La marine marchande" (Box 10)
  - "Mary Kinglsey (1862-1900)," B & M Ltd. (Box 7)
  - "The Mask and the Face," Keliher, Hudson & Kearns Ltd., England (Box 7)
  - "Master Race or Equal Peoples" (Box 7)
  - "Memorial Service for R.A. Personnel," 1945 (Box 14)
  - "Merchant Marine: The Lifeline of Democracy" (Box 9)
  - "The Merchant Navy," Lt. Commander Anthony Kimmins, Re-printed from the Home Service, England, 1941 (Box 7)
  - "Message by the Prime Minister," Ministry of Home Security, England (Box 3)
  - "Message of the Women of the Empire," H.M. The Queen, England (Box 5)
  - "A Message to British Pitmen" (Box 2)
  - "The Might of the Air Force," Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 13)
  - "The Might of the Army," Harrison & Sons, Ltd., London, 1940 (Box 4)
  - "The Might of the Merchant Navy," Odhams (Watford) Ltd., England, 1941 (Box 11)
  - "The Might of the Navy" (Box 6)
  - "The Might of the Navy," L.T.A Robinson Limited, London, 1940 (Box 14)
  - "Mightier Yet!" E & S (Box 4)
  - "The Mighty War Effort of the British Commonwealth" (Box 3)
  - "Ministry of Information Bulletin," Roosevelt, Franklin, H.M. Stationery Office (Box 4)
  - "Ministry of Information Map Service: Book 1-2," Ministry of Information, 1942 (Box 11)
  - "Ministry of Information Map Service: Book 3-12," Ministry of Information, 1943 (Box 11)
  - "The Miracle of the Red Cross," The Fanfare Press, London (Box 9)
  - "La monarchie constitutionelle anglaise," Sir Earnest Barker (Box 17)
  - "More Lime: More Food," E & S (Box 5)
  - "More Ships for the Ocean Highways, Rowland Hilder (Box 11)
  - "More Volunteers For Day-Time A.R.P.," The Ministry of Information, London (Box 2)
  - "The Morrison Shelter: List of Parts" (Box 7)
  - "Mosquitoes Go to War" (Box 10)
  - "Nail That Lie!" Ministry of Information, England (Box 4)
  - "National Day of Prayer 'Put Your Trust in God as I Do' - His Majesty the King, " Ministry of Information (Box 7)
  - "National Renaissance Bulletin," New York, 1953 (Box 3)
  - "Le national-socialisme et le christianisme," Martin Bormann (Box 9)
  - "Nattens soldater..." (Box 11)
  - "Navy Estimates," Winston Churchill, H.M. Stationery Office Press, England, 1940 (Box 5)
  - "The Navy's Part" (Box 9)
  - "Nazi-German in 22 Lessons," G. Pulman & Sons, Ltd., London (Box 3)
  - "Nazis Bomb Civilians" (Box 4)
  - "Nazis Bomb Lightships," England (Box 4)
  - "Nazis or Neighbors," Keliher, Hudson & Kearns, Ltd., England (Box 4)
  - "Neige russe" (Box 13)
  - "Neptune, No.15, 17-20" (Multiple Languages) (Box 13)
  - "Neptune, No.21, 25-27" (Multiple Languages) (Box 13)
  - "Neptune, No. 46, 49, 57" (Multiple Languages) (Box 13)
  - "The New Age" (in Farsi), Hodder & Stoughton Ltd. / Imperial Chemical Industries Ltd., 1944 (Box 6)
  - "The New National Health Service," Central Office of Information (Box 8)
  - "New Order Flag" (Box 4)
  - "News Items," 1-10 June 1943, 1943 (Box 17)
  - "News Items," 11-20 June 1943, 1943 (Box 17)
  - "News Items," 21-30 June 1943, 1943 (Box 17)
  - "Nigeria for Victory," Cockayne & Co., Ltd. (Box 8)
  - "No!" Cockayne & Co. Ltd., England (Box 5)
  - "Northern Rhodesia for Victory," Cockayne & Co., Ltd. (Box 8)
  - "Northolt Airport," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 7)
  - "Notes for European Listeners," K.H.K. (Box 2)
  - "Notes for Married Families in Austria" (2nd Edition), Printing and Sationary Services, 1945 (Box 14)
  - "Notes on Gunners in Far Eastern Theatres" (Box 13)
  - "Notice to Traders and Shipping Firms (European)" England (Box 9)
  - "Notice to Traders and Shipping Firms (Overseas)" England (Box 9)
  - "Les nouvelles de France et du monde" No. 21-36, 1940 (Box 17)
  - "Now and always!" Ministry of Information, England (Box 5)
  - "Nyasaland for Victory," Cockayne & Co. Ltd. (Box 1)
  - "O sistema parlamentar de governo" (Portuguese), Sir Ernest Barker, Oxford University Press (Box 10)
  - "L'offensive aerienne" (Box 11)
  - "Official British Commentary on Herr Hitler's Reichstag Speech," His Majesty's Stationery Office Press, 1939 (Box 1)
  - "Om hulle in die lug te hou," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "On Guard," U.S.A., 1946 (Box 2)
  - "Onslaught by Air,", 1941 (Box 11)
  - "Oorlog in Beeld" No. 3, 4, 7, 13, 24 (Box 15)
  - "Oorlog in Beeld" No. 26-30 (Box 15)
  - "Oorlog in Beeld" No. 31-35 (Box 15)
  - "Oorlog in Beeld" No. 36-40 (Box 15)
  - "Oorlog in Beeld" No. 41, 42, 47, 48, 51 (Box 15)
  - "L'opinion et gouvernement," Sir Henry N. Bunbury, L'Office Central de L'Information, London, 1947 (Box 2)
  - "Organisation of Air Raid Casualties Services," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1938 (Box 10)
  - "Organised Camping Ministry of Education Pamphlet No. 11," His Majesty Stationery Office, London, 1948 (Box 7)
  - "Origins and Purpose," McCorquodale & Co. Ltd., Great Britain (Box 8)
  - "Our Money, How We Get and Spend it," His Majesty's Stationery Office (Box 12)
  - "Outbreak of War," Ministry of London, London, 1939 (Box 2)
  - "An Outline of British Pioneering in Civil Air Transport," The Ministry of Information, London (Box 2)
  - "Outline of the Functions and Work of the Ministry of Labour and National Service," Ernest Bevin, Victoria House Printing Co., Ltd., London, 1942 (Box 2)
  - "Pacific Balance," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Parachute Corps," England (Box 7)
  - "Parliamentary System of Government," Sir Ernest Barker, Oxford University Press (Box 9)
  - "Pastoral Letter," Richard Downey (Box 3)
  - "A People at War" (Box 9)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 2" (Australia), Harrison & Sons Ltd., 1941 (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 3" (New Zealand), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 4" (South Africa), Harrison & Sons Ltd., 1941 (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 5" (India), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 6" (Newfoundland), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 7" (Southern Rhodesia), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 8" (Burma), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 9" (Ceylon), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 10" (Malaya), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 12" (West Africa), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 13" (Malta), Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Peoples of the Empire No. 14" (West Indies), Harrison & Sons, Ltd. (Box 12)
  - "Personnel Requirements for Air Raid General and Fire Precautions Services, and the Police Service," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1938 (Box 6)
  - "Un peuple en guerre," Stevens & B. (Box 3)
  - "A Picture of India," Edwin Haward, Spottiswoode, Balantyne & Co., Ltd. (Box 3)
  - "Pig Scrap and Kitchen Waste Container," E & S, England (Box 4)
  - "Pilots of To-morrow" (Box 12)
  - "Un placement en amitié" (Box 9)
  - "Plan for the New Coventry," H & S, Ltd. (Box 5)
  - "Playing Their Part" Editions 1, 2, 3, and 5 (Box 7)
  - "Pocket Guide to Burma," Fosh & Cross, Ltd., London (Box 6)
  - "O poder da Marinha Mercante" (Box 11)
  - "Poland and Scotland," H.M. Stationery Office (Box 4)
  - "Pour la liberté," Ministry of Information, London, 1941 (Box 4)
  - "Pourquoi la commonwealth Britannique est-elle si unie dans cette guerre?" (Box 14)
  - "The Power Behind Their Wings" (Box 17)
  - "The Power of the Merchant Navy" (in Farsi) (Box 11)
  - "President Roosevelt Quote," The Baynard Press (Box 12)
  - "The Press in War Time," Ministry of Information, 1944 (Box 6)
  - "Principal British Ranks and Insignia" (Box 16)
  - "Progrès et liberté," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "Progress Towards Self-Government in the British Colonies," Kamm, Josephine, Fosh & Cross Ltd. (Box 8)
  - "Protect Your Factory," Ministry of Information & War Office, England (Box 4)
  - "Protecting Crops from Incendiary Bombs" (Box 17)
  - "Protection of Native African Cattle from Disease," British Information Services, New York City (Box 5)
  - "Protection of Windows in Commercial and Industrial Buildings," His Majesty's Stationery Office, London, 1940 (Box 6)
  - "La puissance de la Marine Marchande" /"Die Mag van de Handelsvloot" (Box 14)
  - "Put Ye on the Armour of God," E & S, England (Box 3)
  - "Quatorze juillet" (Box 10)
  - "Quatre années de guerre...par les cartes,", 1943 (Box 13)
  - "Ranks and Insignia," Thos. Forman & Sons Ltd. (Box 7)
  - "Rationing of Food in Great Britain" (Box 6)
  - "Le Rationnement en Angleterre," Sir Ernest Barker (Box 17)
  - "Rats,", 1945 (Box 13)
  - "The Real Struggle," Harrison & Sons, Ltd., England, 1941 (Box 5)
  - "Rebuilding Great Britain," British Information Services, B & M Ltd., London (Box 2)
  - "La reconstrucción de la Gran Bretana en la postguerra," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "La reconstruction de la Grande Bretagne après la guerre" (Box 17)
  - "Red Cross and St. John need every penny you can spare," War Organisation of the British Red Cross Society (Box 5)
  - "Red Cross and St. John, The Student Prisoner, More Books Urgently Needed," The Fanfare Press, 1944 (Box 13)
  - "The Red Snow" (Box 5)
  - "Regional Pattern of the U.S.A," Harrison & Sons Ltd., London (Box 12)
  - "The Regular Army," War Office, England, 1948 (Box 4)
  - "Report of Inter-departmental Committee on the Rehabilitation and Resettlement of Disabled Persons," His Majesty's Stationary Office, 1943 (Box 13)
  - "Resurgam" (Box 5)
  - "La retraite des vieux,", 1941 (Box 1)
  - "La Reunion en Atlantique" (Box 8)
  - "Revolt in the Dark," Fosh & Cross Ltd., London (Box 4)
  - "Révolte dans l'ombre," England (Box 8)
  - "Rising Might of Britain," Neville Chamberlain, Times Publishing Company, Ltd., London, 1940 (Box 4)
  - "The Road to Victory" (Box 6)
  - "Le roi et la reine de l'empire britannique," England (Box 9)
  - "Royal Air Force (R.A.F.)," British Information Services, New York City, 1943 (Box 1)
  - "Royal Air Force Log Book" (Box 2)
  - "The Royal Air Force School for Prisoners of War," Red Cross & St. John Organisation (Box 10)
  - "The Royal Netherlands Navy," Divine, A.D. (Box 10)
  - "Royal Warrants and Orders Concerning Pensions and Awards, " His Majesty's Stationary Office, 1945 (Box 14)
  - "Saga of the Seafire" (Box 9)
  - "The Same Aggressor," L.T.A. Robinson, Ltd., London, 1941 (Box 3)
  - "Sea Power's Daily Task," Spottiswoode, Ballantyne and Co. Ltd., London (Box 2)
  - "Sea-War,", 1943 (Box 5)
  - "La sécurité sociale en Angleterre," Stevens & B, 1946 (Box 16)
  - "September 15th, 1940: A Day That Will Live Forever" (Box 7)
  - "Serve to Conquer with Me...in the ATS," England (Box 5)
  - "The Services Handbook," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Les services sociaux en Angleterre," Wauters, Arthur (Box 16)
  - "Short Guide to Some Agencies of International Co-Operation," Ministry of Information, 1945 (Box 7)
  - "Sierra Leone for Victory," Cockayne & Co., Ltd. (Box 8)
  - "Silently She Slipped Away," England (Box 4)
  - "Sixty Million of Us" (Box 4)
  - "De slag om Groot-Brittannië," 1940 (Box 17)
  - "Social Security in Britain 1948," Great Britain (Box 7)
  - "Social Services in the Colonies: Part I, Background to Social Policy," Ministry of Information (Box 8)
  - "Social Services in the Colonies: Part II," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Social Services in the Colonies: Part III," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Social Services in the Colonies: Part IV, Health," Ministry of Information (Box 8)
  - "Social Services in the Colonies: Part V," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "Some Facts about Britain," Inbel, London, 1943 (Box 9)
  - "Something Done," Birch, Lionel, His Majesty's Stationery Office, London (Box 14)
  - "Something to Give..." (Box 5)
  - "Southern U.S.A. States," Harrison & Sons, Ltd., London (Box 12)
  - "A Spear for Freedom," British Ministry of Information, New York City (Box 2)
  - "Special Collections in the Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace," Almond, Nina and Fisher, A. A., Stanford University, California, 1940 (Box 8)
  - "The Special Secretariat," Ministry of Information, London, 1940 (Box 4)
  - "Special Secretariat" letters, Coropen, Duff, Ministry of Information, London, 2 Aug. 1940 (Box 5)
  - "A Speech by the Prime Minister," Churchill, Winston, The Baynard Press, 1940 (Box 4)
  - "Speech, by Viscount Halifax," English Speaking Union, New York, 1941 (Box 1)
  - "Spirit and Aims of Britain in War," Temple, William, B.B.C., 1939 (Box 5)
  - "Stamping Out the U-Boats!" Fosh & Cross Ltd., England (Box 4)
  - "Stay Where You Are," Ministry of Information & War Office, England (Box 4)
  - "Stay Where You Are," Ministry of Information, War Office, Ministry of Home Security, England (Box 4)
  - "Stepping Stones in Western Defence" (Box 11)
  - "Stone Masonry," His Majesty's Stationery Office, 1949 (Box 10)
  - "Storbritannias hjemmevern," Anglo-Amerikanske Informasjonstjeneste (Box 14)
  - "The Story of Burma: Part II," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "The Story of Burma: Part III," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "The Strength of Navies After Nine Months of War," England, 1940 (Box 2)
  - "The Structure of British Empire," Ministry of Information (Box 8)
  - "The Struggle for Freedom,", 1940 (Box 12)
  - "Le système parlementaire Anglais," Barker, Earnest (Sir) (Box 17)
  - "Talking Points: August 6th 1941 - August 27th 1941" (Box 11)
  - "Talking Points: July 31st 1941 - October 15th 1941," Greycaines (Box 11)
  - "Talking Points: June 4th 1941 - July 30th 1941" (Box 11)
  - "Tanganyika for Victory," Cockayne & Co. Ltd. (Box 1)
  - "Target" Vol. 2 No. 10, Central Office of Information (Box 12)
  - "Thank You," Women's Voluntary Services for Civil Defence, London (Box 6)
  - "'The Halkevi' (People's House) in Turkey" (Box 10)
  - "Theiler of Onderstepoort," B & M Ltd. (Box 7)
  - "Their Majesties King George VI and Queen Elizabeth," Hubners Ltd., England (Box 4)
  - "These Names Make Victories" (Box 1)
  - "They Don't Want Swamps and Jungles," Knight, Eric, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (Box 9)
  - "They Fight by Night" (Box 13)
  - "They're Not Allowed to be Children," Ministry of Information, England (Box 5)
  - "This is the People's War,", 1940 (Box 17)
  - "This Man Said: 'I Like War'," News Chronicle, England, 22 Jan. 40 (Box 4)
  - "Thomas Stamford Raffles," B & M Ltd. (Box 4)
  - "The Thousand Year Reich," Ministry of Information (Box 6)
  - "To all Frenchmen...," Gaulle, Charles de (General), London (Box 10)
  - "To All of the Frenchmen," Fosh & Cross Ltd., London (Box 4)
  - "To Editors of Works and Staff Magazines" (Box 17)
  - "To Help You Settle in Britain," Central Office of Information, Great Britain, 1948 (Box 8)
  - "Today" No. 6, 20-22, 24, Central Office of Information, London (Box 16)
  - "Total Victory Call by Mr. Roosevelt" (Box 12)
  - "Tours for United States Armed Forces," B & M Ltd. (Box 5)
  - "The Trade Unionist and the War," Tracey, Herbert (Box 6)
  - "Las 'Trade Unions' Britanicas y la guerra," Price, John, Stevens & B, 1946 (Box 16)
  - "Trechu'r Goresgynndd" (Box 12)
  - "Trinidad for Victory," Cockayne & Co. Ltd. (Box 4)
  - "A Trip in a Giant Bomber" (Box 9)
  - "Truth in Chains" (Box 8)
  - "Tutto un popolo lavora per la vittoria," Stevens & B. (Box 1)
  - "Twelve New Allies" (Box 3)
  - "Twenty-Five Years Young," Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 9)
  - "Twice-Raped Louvain," Guppy, Henry (Dr.), England, 1940 (Box 2)
  - "Two Mighty Fleets,", 1943 (Box 2)
  - "U.S.A.: The Making of a Nation," Harrison & Sons Ltd. (Box 11)